Guide to the Jaime Davidovich Collection MSS.155
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series V: Artifacts and Objects
  - Subseries B: Television Collection
    - Plastic TV salt and pepper shaker. Shakers slide out of the television-shaped holder. The "on" dial elevates the shakers., undated (Box 27, Folder 155.2.0036)
    - Brown ceramic television shaped salt and pepper shakers. Top monitor is salt, base is pepper., undated (Box 27, Folder 155.2.0037)
    - Dollhouse furniture: Lounge Suite. Original packaging. 5 pieces, miniature sofa, two chairs, coffee table and a television., undated (Box 27, Folder 155.2.0038)
    - TV Time play puzzle. Plastic television shaped puzzle. Screen comes apart in six pieces. Depicts a bear driving a car. TV has moveable antenna, a button that beeps, and a dial that clicks. Still in original box and plastic fillm., undated (Box 28, Folder 155.2.0039)
    - Television Christmas tree ornament multiple. Three paper ornaments. TV screen shows a burning yule log behind a plastic screen. Designed by Jaime Davidovich., undated (Box 28, Folder 155.2.0040)
    - Dukes of hazzard TV tray. Child's size blue TV tray with photo of the Duke sof Hazzard and Daisy with a guitar. "Carla" etched into th epaint on the bottom edge of the tray. Made by Warner Bros. Inc., 1981 (Box 31, Folder 155.2.0041)
    - Watch Highclass. Two watches mounted on a cardboard display that is printed to look like a televisioin showing a baseball game., undated (Box 31, Folder 155.2.0042)
    - "Don't Watch TV at the table!" placemat. Laminated placemat displaying images of historical televisions. Made by Paper Tales, Ltd., 1991 (Box 31, Folder 155.2.0043)
    - Winky Dink and You. Winky Dink set, still sealed in original packaging. Made by Standard ToyKraft Products., undated (Box 31, Folder 155.2.0045)
  - Subseries C: ATN and the Live! Show
    - TeeVee rubber stamp. Red, wooden handle., undated. (Box 24, Folder 155.2.0001)
    - Foam TV costume, undated (Box 33, Object 155.2.0001a, Object 155.2.0001b)
    - "The Live! Show" rubber stamp, red wooden base, black wooden handle., undated. (Box 24, Folder 155.2.0002)
    - Hand held paper emobosser with Artists' Television Network Inc. Corporate Seal., ca 1976 (Box 24, Folder 155.2.0003)
    - Kaleidoscope. Two parts. Black box with paper label. Square hole in the bottom of the box secured with tape. Inside, a black cardboard cylinder with a black label, round hole in the top. Inside the cylinder is white with mirror at back. Made by Stefan Eins., 1976 (Box 24, Folder 155.2.0004)
    - "The Live! Show" t-shirt. Blue short sleeved t-shirt with silk screened image of television shaped object with a "Live! Show" button on its screen. The TV object is part of the collection, object I.D. 155.2.0035., undated. (Box 24, Folder 155.2.0034)
    - Dr. Videovich lab coat. Long sleeved, white lab coat with three pockets. Multicolored "The Live! Show" buttons pepper the front of the costume. "Dr Videovich" in black paint on the reverse. TV sunglasses in one of the pockets. Made by Jaime Davidovich., undated. (Box 32, Folder 155.2.0044)
    - The Live! Show backdrop, Undated; 155.2.0058; 1 item one banner (Item MSS.155.2.0058, Item 155.2.0058)
      Banners.
  - Subseries D: Portapak
    - Sony AV-3400 Video Camera. (Box 29, Folder 155.2.0054)
    - Sony AC-1000 power/Battery Charger (Box 30, Folder 155.2.0055)
    - Sony Av-8400S Color Portable Video System. Second generation 1/2 inc EIAJ portapak (Box 29, Folder 155.2.0056)
    - Operating Instructions, Sony AV-8400S (Box 29, Folder 155.2.0057)
- Series VI: Administrative Materials
  This series includes administrative materials such as grant information and resumes that relate to Jaime Davidovich's professional career. The series is divided into six subseries. Subseries A: Resumes includes drafts and updated resumes and CVs. Subseries B: Contacts includes addressbooks, mailing lists and other contact information. Subseries C: Professional Organizations and Opportunities includes publicity information and membership information regarding professional art organizations and professional opportunities including grants and residencies. Subseries D: Grants contains grant applications and supporting materials. Subseries E: Loans consists of loan requests, agreements, contracts, and receipts. Subseries F: Equipment and Manuals contains directions and owner's manuals for appliances, tools, and audio-visiual equipment.
  - Subseries A: Resumes
    - Informal artist profile portfolio including press, resume, black and white prints, and color slides. Grouped by J.D., 1971-1984 (Box 13, Folder 650)
    - Jaime Davidovich, videotapes Catalog, 1972-1976 (Box 13, Folder 651)
    - Videography, 1972-1980 (Box 13, Folder 652)
    - Resume, original, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 653)
    - Resumes, drafts., 1995 (Box 13, Folder 654)
    - Resume, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 655)
    - Resume, draft, ca 1997 (Box 13, Folder 656)
    - Resume, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 657)
    - Teaching Resume, undated (Box 13, Folder 658)
    - Resume and Avalance advertisement, undated (Box 13, Folder 659)
  - Subseries B: Contacts
    - Address book, Argentina, undated (Box 13, Folder 660)
    - Address book, Argentina, undated (Box 13, Folder 661)
    - Argentine Mailing List, undated (Box 13, Folder 662)
    - Argentine contacts, undated (Box 13, Folder 663)
    - Consulate General of Argentina Mailing list., undated (Box 13, Folder 664)
    - Contacts, undated (Box 13, Folder 665)
    - ICI Notes and business card., undated (Box 13, Folder 666)
    - Scars, pleasure, sacrifice exhibit mailing list., 1994 (Box 13, Folder 667)
  - Subseries C: Professional Organizations and Opportunities
    - "Video Tape 1975" includes multiple video organizations in US (Box 13, Folder 668)
    - Participate Public Access Report, 1985-1986 (Box 13, Folder 669)
    - ArtCom Television., 1986 (Box 13, Folder 670)
    - Alternative Museum Membership, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 671)
    - Residency Programs and Grants, 1996-1997 (Box 13, Folder 672)
    - Mid-Career Latino Artists. Inc. minutes and memo., 1997 (Box 13, Folder 673)
    - National Video Resources., 1997 (Box 13, Folder 674)
    - Residency Programs and Grants, 1997-1998 (Box 13, Folder 675)
    - Lower Manhattan Cultural Council, "World Views" artists in residence program, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 676)
    - Thunder Gulch, press and PR packet., 1998 (Box 13, Folder 677)
    - FVA membership, undated (Box 13, Folder 678)
  - Subseries D: Grants
    - NEA Fellowship, 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 679)
    - Torn Identity, supplementary material booklet., 1979 (Box 15, Folder 680)
    - NEA applications, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 681)
    - NEA, 1983-1984 (Box 15, Folder 682)
    - Torn Identity videotape project, NYSCA application forms, 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 683)
    - Audience 1990 Description (Box 15, Folder 684)
    - Rockefeller Proposal, Inside/Outside Installation, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 685)
    - USIA blakc forms and instructions, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 686)
    - United States Information Agency, Official Grant Packet, including Grant Authorization and voucher, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 687)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, visual Artists fellowship archive, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 688)
  - Subseries E: Loan agreements, receipts, release forms
    - Akron Art Institute Invitational, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 689)
    - MoMA Video VII, "3 Mercer St" loan contract, receipt, publicity materials., 1976 (Box 15, Folder 690)
    - Model release for "Best Artist" interview at Whitney Downtown., 1982 (Box 15, Folder 691)
    - Model release, Charles Simpson for "SoHo So What?", 1983 (Box 15, Folder 692)
    - Consent forms, "Evita", 1983 (Box 15, Folder 693)
    - Loan agreements, "From receiver to remote control: The TV Set", 1980 (Box 15, Folder 694)
    - London Video Access, royalty payment for John Cage Tape., 1994 (Box 15, Folder 695)
    - Sotheby's and Christy's, inquiries into auctioning Jack Berthot painting, "Egypt", 1995 (Box 15, Folder 696)
    - Storage Space, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 697)
    - Legacy/Legado, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 698)
    - Talas Archival invoices, 1996-1997 (Box 15, Folder 699)
    - Press pass- Mediapolis Magazine., 1997 (Box 15, Folder 700)
    - United States Information Agency, receipts, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 701)
    - Lux, distribution of royalties for "The Gap" videotape., 1999 (Box 15, Folder 702)
    - Copyright releases, master form, undated (Box 15, Folder 703)
  - Subseries F:Equipment and manuals
    - "Editing with the Sony EV-320F" directions, undated (Box 15, Folder 704)
    - Instruction and Care manuals: includes power tools and video equipment., undated (Box 15, Folder 705)
    - Media Alliance, Magnetic media Preservation Sourcebook, edited by Mona Jimenez and Liss Platt., 1998 (Box 15, Folder 706)
    - Video Walls, undated (Box 15, Folder 707)
- Series VII: Other Artists
  This series contains works, exhibition information, and press pertaining to other artists. Series A: Mail Art Album includes items including postcards removed from a binder. Items are organized to reflect the binder's organization. Subseries B: Announcements and Works includes materials organized by artist name.
  - Subseries A: Mail Art Album
    - Inserts in Postcards binder, undated (Box 15, Folder 708)
    - Page 1, four items. John Taylor, Beach Blacket Bingo; Dieter Rot; Leonhard Frank Duch; Joan Crawford Mother's Day Celebration., undated (Box 15, Folder 709)
    - Page 2, six items. Marcel Just, Shigeko, Alan Platt x 3, [illegible], undated (Box 15, Folder 710)
    - Page 3, five items. Martha Wilson, Raul, Nam June Paik, Jill Kroesen, unknown., undated (Box 15, Folder 711)
    - Page 4, four tiems. Mel, Committee for Visual Arts, Robert Kushner, Paul McMahon., undated (Box 15, Folder 712)
    - Page 5, four items. R.M. Fischer, Richard Prince, Susan King, Marja Samsom., undated (Box 15, Folder 713)
    - Page 6, seven items. Guglielmo Achille Cavellini postcard and stickers, Kit Fitzgerald and John Sanbormn, Peter Downsbrough, undated (Box 15, Folder 714)
    - Page 7, four items. Peter Grass, Carla Davidovich, Pierre Ducordeau, Jonathan Willilams, undated (Box 15, Folder 715)
    - Page 9, five items. Marroquin-Verhoeven, Investigation department card, Ilene Segalove x 2, Dieter, undated (Box 15, Folder 716)
    - Page 10, four items. Bill Indigo, Stuart Sherman, Michael Morris, Centre de Documentacio d'art actual, Barcelona., 1979 (Box 15, Folder 717)
    - Page 11, four items. J. Davidovich, Liliana Porter, Doug Smith and Tom Bagg, "The Answer Wasn't Here", undated (Box 15, Folder 718)
    - Page 12, four items.Shigeko, Tom Baggs, Mitchell Kriegman, Ken Graves, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 719)
    - Page 13, twelve items. Raul Marroquin, Nikolaus Urban, Myrel Chernick, Reudi Schill., undated (Box 15, Folder 720)
    - Page 14, four items. Yves de Smet, Nikolaus Urban, Johan, Jac and Marion., 1976-1980 (Box 15, Folder 721)
    - Page 15, ten items. Raul Marroquin, Ruedi Schill x6, Tony Morgan, Kazuo Katase., undated (Box 15, Folder 722)
    - Page 16, four items. Linda Blumberg, SoHo TV at The Kitchen, Anthony McCall, Beth Anderson with Paul Cotton., undated (Box 15, Folder 723)
    - Page 174 items. Shigeko Kubota, Stefan Eins, Raul Marroquin, Muntadas/Serran-Pagan., undated (Box 15, Folder 724)
    - Page 18, five items. Brian Lane [two little books], Kitasono Katue, Helena Kontova, John Gordon., undated (Box 15, Folder 725)
    - Page 19, six items. Live from San Francisco, Ken Feingold, unknown sender of Wooster Inc. Envelope card, Donald, R.m. Fischer, Beyond Novelty and Boredom., undated (Box 15, Folder 726)
    - Page 20, six items. Bonnie and Clyde Stuff, Invite to reception with Dr. Carlos Menem, Barbara Kruger matchbooks, Jeanette, You connect the dots., undated (Box 15, Folder 727)
    - Page 21, five items. Steve Lawrence and Sergei Miroshnichenko, Guillermo Kuitra, Bound and Unbound Wooster Enterprises, Jeanette, Stuart., 1989, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 728)
    - Page 22, twenty items. Points of view stereograph postcards x6, Joe Brainard's "Twelve Postcards", Donald Baechler, Kesa., undated (Box 15, Folder 729)
    - Page 23, four items. Ben Mark Holzberg, Pierre Ducordeau, Susan Hilton, Willyum Rowe., undated (Box 15, Folder 730)
    - Page 24, six items. Raul Morroquin, Hans Eykelboom, Marroquin and Young Tchong, Kazuo Katase x3, undated (Box 15, Folder 731)
    - Page 25, four items. Carroll Dunham, Ger Van Dijck, Raul Marroquin, Tom Rubnitz., undated (Box 15, Folder 732)
    - Page 26, four items. Nam June Paik, Eva and Juan Peron cards., undated (Box 15, Folder 733)
    - Page 27, nine items. Nam June Paik x2, Pieter L. Mol, Matlin and McConnell, Architecture Sequences exhibit, Reudi Schill series "landschaftsgeschichte", undated (Box 15, Folder 734)
    - Page 28, six items. Silvia Kolbowski, Eileen Hickey, Anthology of Film Archives Series Courthouse Building x5, Univeristy Community Video., undated (Box 15, Folder 735)
    - Page 29, four items. Justine of Colette is Dead Co.; Camillo, Mel Andrainga and John Herbert; Dieter Frosse x2., undated (Box 15, Folder 736)
    - Page 30, five items. E.F. Higgins III x2, Dieter Froese x2, Art TV., undated (Box 15, Folder 737)
    - Page 31, 4 items. Fernando de Filippi, Eric Bogosian, Nicole Gravier, Dieter Froese., 1979 (Box 15, Folder 738)
  - Subseries B: Announcements and Works
    - Cal Arts, "8 Faces", undated (Box 15, Folder 739)
    - Filomia, Carlos., undated (Box 15, Folder 740)
    - Fontana, TV Manifesto., undated (Box 15, Folder 741)
    - Goldman, Ilene. Book proposal: Wandering the Nation., 1996 (Box 15, Folder 742)
    - Group Ojo, "el ojo en NY" color negatives and photographs of street art., undated (Box 15, Folder 743)
    - Howell, Sue. Black and white photographs of Sue Howell with TV, photographs by Otway Chalkley., 1981 (Box 15, Folder 745)
    - Ingberg, Pablo., undated (Box 15, Folder 746)
    - "Mighty Mogul" (Box 15, Folder 747)
    - Paksa, Margarita., undated (Box 15, Folder 748)
    - Puzzovio, Dalila., undated (Box 15, Folder 749)
    - Wentscher, Herbert. Cartoons of TVs, undated (Box 15, Folder 750)
    - Yahlovith, Nina, undated (Box 15, Folder 751)
- Series VIII: Source Material
  This series contains source materials. Subseries A: Scrap Books includes images of televisions and other source materials that were grouped into three binders labeled here as A, B, and C. Materials retain the order in which they appeared in the original books. Subseries B: Subject Files includes paper files organized alphabetically by publication, project, or theme. Materials include maps, periodicals, brochures and other paperwork.
  - Subseries A: Scrap Books
    - TVs Binder A,inserts. Large color photograph and line drawing., undated (Box 15, Folder 752)
    - TVsBinder A, page 1. Bunch of Artists postcard, advertisement for Selfmaker folding tray-tables., undated (Box 15, Folder 753)
    - TVs Binder A, page 2. TV greeting cards, undated (Box 15, Folder 754)
    - TVs Binder A, page 3. 5 color photographs of foam Sony TV sculpture and postcard., undated (Box 15, Folder 755)
    - TVs Binder A, page 4. 2 large black and white video stills and a color magazine image., undated (Box 15, Folder 756)
    - TVs Binder A, page 5. 4 color photographs of Jaime Davidovich with foam Sony TV., undated (Box 15, Folder 757)
    - TVs Binder A, page 6. TV birthday card and two large black and white video stills., undated (Box 15, Folder 758)
    - TVs Binder A, page 7. 1 large black and white video still, one color photograph of TV window display., undated (Box 15, Folder 759)
    - TVs Binder A, page 8. SoHo TV postcard, Liza Bear opening postcard, TV themed greeting card, and color snapshot of a TV in a car., undated (Box 15, Folder 760)
    - TVs Binder A, page 9. 2 postcards, 2 color snapshots., undated (Box 15, Folder 761)
    - TVs Binder A, page10. 11 color postcards., undated (Box 15, Folder 762)
    - TVs Binder A, page 11. 2 copies of 2 television themed greeting cards., undated (Box 15, Folder 763)
    - TVs Binder A, page 12. 3 television themed greeting cards, 2 different styles., undated (Box 15, Folder 764)
    - TVs Binder A, page 13. 3 television themed greeting cards, two styles., undated (Box 15, Folder 765)
    - TVs Binder A, page 14. 2 television themed greeting cards., undated (Box 15, Folder 766)
    - TVs Binder A, page 15. 2 television themed greeting cards., undated (Box 15, Folder 767)
    - TVs Binder A, page 16. 3 color snapshots and 3 postcards., undated (Box 15, Folder 768)
    - TVs Binder B, page 1-3. 8 color snapsots., undated (Box 15, Folder 769)
    - TVs Binder B, page 4-7. 16 "I Love Lucy" postcards., undated (Box 15, Folder 770)
    - TVs Binder B, page 8-10. 3 postcards, 6 color snapshots and 1 black and white photograph., undated (Box 15, Folder 771)
    - TVs Binder B, page 11-12. 3 carsds, 7 color snapshots., undated (Box 15, Folder 772)
    - TVs Binder B, page 16-19. magazine advertisements, black and white photographs of objects from TV collection, 4 postcard invitations, 1 color photograph., undated (Box 15, Folder 773)
    - TVs Binder B, page 20-22. 2 black and white photographs, 2 color photographs, 1 annotated envelope., undated (Box 15, Folder 774)
    - TVs Binder C, page 1-4. 5 postcarsds, advertisement for Children's Room Shelving, 5 color photographys, photographic image of TV grafitti on paper., undated (Box 15, Folder 775)
    - TVs Binder C, page 5-7. 3 large photographic images printed on paper, TV themed birthday card, photocopy of political cartoon., undated (Box 15, Folder 776)
    - TVs Binder C, page 8-11. 2 color photographs and numerous paper images of TVs., undated (Box 15, Folder 777)
    - TVs Binder C, page 12-14. "The Flintstones: The Birthday Cake" spiral bound book, two color photographs and 3 postcards., undated (Box 15, Folder 778)
    - TVs Binder C, page 15-18. 7 photographs., undated (Box 15, Folder 779)
    - TVs Binder C, page 19-22. 6 large photographs and a small painting of the "Today" show set., undated (Box 15, Folder 780)
    - TVs Binder C, page 6 photographs and 7 printed images of TVs, undated (Box 15, Folder 781)
    - TVs Binder C, page 25-28 9 color photographs. 3 paper images., undated (Box 15, Folder 782)
    - TVs Binder C, page 29-31. 3 photographs, one greeting card and two papers., undated (Box 15, Folder 783)
    - TVs Binder C, page 32-35. 3 greeting cards, one ET trading card and one color photograph of Dr. Videovich in foam TV costume. (Box 15, Folder 784)
  - Subseries B: Subject Files
    - Argentina, includes maps, press, brochures., undated (Box 15, Folder 785A)
    - Argentina, advertisements, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 786)
    - Argentine restaurant in Germany, menu., undated (Box 16, Folder 787)
    - Arts Magazine., 1991 (Box 16, Folder 788)
    - Fundacion Banco Patricos, 1991-1992 (Box 16, Folder 789)
    - Latin American Film and TV, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 790)
    - Marketing, Advertising, and Cultural Production., 1996 (Box 16, Folder 791)
    - Mediapolis, vol.4 n.6, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 792)
    - Menem, Carlos., 1995 (Box 16, Folder 793)
    - New China Restaurant Menu, Kingston New York., undated (Box 16, Folder 794)
    - New York Magazine,"SoHo: The Most Exciting Place to Live in the City" May 20, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 795)
    - New York Magazine, parts cut out on page 3 and page 62, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 796)
    - New York Magazine, " After SoHo, creating new neighborhoods…" April 17, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 797)
    - New York Magazine, December 16. 1985 (Box 16, Folder 798)
    - Peppermint Lounge Fliers, "VJ meets DJ" (Box 16, Folder 799)
    - Point of Contact, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 800)
    - Representations of television sets in print media., undated (Box 16, Folder 801)
    - Representations of video in print media, undated (Box 16, Folder 802)
    - Seibel, Beatriz. "El Cantar del Payador", 1991 (Box 16, Folder 803)
    - Sisley magazine, cover feature: "Argentina te quiero!", 1988 (Box 16, Folder 804)
    - SoHo community organizing newsletters. Used for SoHo, So What?, undated (Box 16, Folder 805)
    - SoHo neighborhood development., 1996 (Box 16, Folder 806)
    - Symbol Magazine no. 1, Spring, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 806a)
    - Symbol Magazine no. 4, Winter, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 806b)
    - TV shaped objects, 6 color snapshots and two black and white photographs., undated (Box 16, Folder 807)
    - TV images, not photographic, undated (Box 16, Folder 808)
    - Torn Identity source material: National Lampoon March 1991, The Atlantic December 1990., 1990-1991 (Box 16, Folder 809)
    - Miscellaneous Source material, undated (Box 16, Folder 810)
- Series IX: Family Related
  This series contains materials related to Jaime Davidovich's family including correspondence, photographs, and objects belonging to his children. The series is divided into two subseries by material type. Subseries A: Photographs contains family snapshots and portraits. Subseries B: Paper Documents includes correspondence, coloring books, and legal documents.
  - Subseries A: Photographs
    - Snapshots, Argentina. 9 photographs., undated (Box 16, Folder 811)
    - Large black and white portrait., undated (Box 16, Folder 812)
    - Black and white group portrait., undated (Box 16, Folder 813)
    - Miscellaneous snapshots, 3 photographs., undated (Box 16, Folder 814)
    - Family photographs, black and white negatives, contacts, and prints., undated (Box 16, Folder 815)
    - "Argentina" black and white contact sheets., undated (Box 16, Folder 816)
    - "Argentina Carla" color negatives., undated (Box 16, Folder 817)
  - Subseries B: Paper Documents
    - Argentina- Local-Departamento Orders Book, ToTo. 1978-1981 (Box 16, Folder 818)
    - Argentina-Local-Departamento. Orders Book, ToTo 1978-1981, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 819)
    - Argentina-Local-Departamento. Orders Book, ToTo 1978-1981, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 820)
    - Argentina-Local-Departamento. Orders Book, ToTo 1978-1981 (Box 16, Folder 821)
    - "Argentina- Dept Tablada Etc", 1981 (Box 16, Folder 822)
    - Copa Mudial publicity materials and souveniers, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 823)
    - Nina and Carla Davidovich, notebooks., 1978 (Box 16, Folder 824)
- Oversize Materials
  - Series 1B: Jaime Davidovich,Production; Oversize
    - "Evita" drawing of installation setup., 1984-1992 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Fundacion Banco Patricios, photocopied brochure, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - "Point of Contact" notes, transcript and sketches, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Series 1D: Jaime Davidovich,Exhibition Catalogs, Publicity, and Press; Oversize
    - 12th Annual Avant Garde Festival of New York, poster., 1975 (Folder 9)
    - New American Filmmaker series at the Whitney, advertising poster., 1976 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Bienal de la Habana, poster and schedule., 1984 (Folder 6 Left)
    - Unconstitutional Constitutional Convention, publicity, 1986 (Folder 7 Left)
    - "The Latin American Spirit, Art and Artists in the United States, 1920-1970. Photocopy of essay from exhibit catalog, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - "Contexto Transcultural Video-Instalaciones" at Instituto de Cooperacion Iberoamericana (ICI), schedule., 1990 (Folder 4 Left)
    - "Los pueblox quieren saber de que se trata" at Fundacion Banco Patricios, posters., 1992 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - "Lo Falso, Lo Virtual, Lo Real" exhibition at ICI, Davidovich work "Recordando el Futuro" featured. Posters., 1994 (Folder 1 Right)
    - "la Tierra Prometida" at ICI, Buenos Aires. Publicity and scheduling posters., 1995 (Folder 5 Left)
    - El Museo del Barrio 25th Anniversary Exhibition catalog., 1995 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - "Legacy/Legado" exhibition, press., 1996 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - 3rd exhibition of Euroamerican video and digital art, event calendar, 1998 (Box 35, Folder 4)